Here at JOCO we have the upmost respect for your privacy and value our relationship with our customers. We are committed to responsible information practices. Because we gather certain types of information to process orders, we want you to understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it.

ALL personal information collected on jococups.com is transmitted over an industry standard 128 bit secure SSL connection using our bank, and never passed on to third parties.

**The Information we collect**

In general, you can browse our Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.

There are a few places where we give you an opportunity to provide to us your personal information. This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities on our web site – such as ordering a product, joining our mailing list, filling out a survey, sending us feedback, making trade or information enquiries – we may ask you to provide certain information. If you choose to share any personal information with us, you will see that the amount and type of personal information we request depend on how you use our Web site. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities.

If you elect to engage in these activities, however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address, email address, telephone, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products on our web site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

**How we use the information**

Our delivery partners use your address for delivery, but will not pass them on to any third parties. We do not pass on, sell or swap any of your personal details with anyone else. We use this information to identify your orders, provide you with JOCO updates (if requested) and to personalise your shopping experience with us.

**Google Analytics**

We’re currently using Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to gather information for site improvement. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings here – https://www.google.com/settings/ads

### **CREDIT CARDS**

Credit card details are securely collected at the time of payment for the sole purpose of transmitting to the banks for processing. No credit card information is ever physically stored in JOCO’s database. We use Pay Pal for all transactions. More information on Pay Pal’s Legal Agreements can be found at [Pay Pal](https://cms.paypal.com/au/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Legal_Hub_full&locale.x=en_AU).

We are committed to the Privacy Principles under the Privacy Act 1988 – available at: [http://www.privacy.gov.au/publications/ipps.html](http://www.privacy.gov.au/publications/ipps.html)
